=The Forbidden Woman=
= المرأة المحرمة =
=Episode 2=
= الحلقة 2 =
I'm getting some fresh air up here.
أحصل على بعض الهواء النقي هنا.
Dear.
عزيزي.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Hmph!
همف!
Fengyan.
فنغيان.
You may go in.
يمكنك الدخول.
All right.
حسنا.
Wei.
وي.
Did you see anything just now?
هل رأيت أي شيء الآن؟
What was it?
ماذا كان؟
No, I didn't.
لا ، لم أفعل.
You better stop doing such silly acts.
من الأفضل أن تتوقف عن فعل مثل هذه الأفعال السخيفة.
You've embarrassed Dad
لقد أحرجت أبي
and Fengyan.
وفنغيان.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
After all, I'm the elder daughter of Xiang's family
بعد كل شيء ، أنا الابنة الكبرى لعائلة شيانغ
and the rightful successor.
والخليفة الشرعي.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
I really envy you sometimes.
أنا حقا أحسدك في بعض الأحيان.
What do you envy me?
ماذا تحسدني؟
Because you're born out of wedlock.
لأنك ولدت خارج إطار الزواج.
No one will notice you
لن يلاحظك أحد
no matter what you've done.
مهما فعلت.
Clive Christian.
كلايف كريستيان.
This high-end fragrance doesn't suit you well.
هذا العطر الراقي لا يناسبك جيدًا.
It's not slutty enough.
انها ليست بصورة عاهرة بما فيه الكفاية.
Xiang Wei.
شيانغ وي.
I'll claim everything
سأطالب بكل شيء
from you.
منك.
Ms. Xiang.
السيدة شيانغ.
How could
كيف يمكن
a woman who can't even uncap a bottle
امرأة لا تستطيع حتى نزع غطاء الزجاجة
have enough strength to fight with others?
لديك القوة الكافية للقتال مع الآخرين؟
I'm curious about something.
أشعر بالفضول حيال شيء ما.
Do you have a girlfriend?
هل لديك صديقة؟
No.
لا.
You're being mean to a woman you meet for the first time.
أنت تتعامل مع امرأة تقابلها للمرة الأولى.
This explains why you're single.
هذا ما يفسر سبب كونك أعزب.
This is not our first time meeting each other.
هذه ليست المرة الأولى التي نلتقي فيها ببعضنا البعض.
Oh.
أوه.
I remember it.
أتذكرها.
You're the successor of Chu's family.
أنت خليفة عائلة تشو.
My name is Chu Yumo,
اسمي تشو يومو ،
not Chu's successor.
ليس خليفة تشو.
I need to leave now.
أنا بحاجة للمغادرة الآن.
By the way,
على فكرة،
as for what you did just now,
بالنسبة لما فعلته الآن ،
thank you.
شكرا لك.
Were you really jumping off the balcony?
هل كنت حقا تقفز من الشرفة؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
I think so.
أعتقد ذلك.
Had you killed yourself,
لو قتلت نفسك
you wouldn't have chosen a low-level building.
لم تكن لتختار مبنى منخفض المستوى.
You...
أنت...
When I converse with you,
عندما أتحدث معك ،
I feel like I've travelled back to five years ago,
أشعر وكأنني سافرت إلى الوراء منذ خمس سنوات ،
somehow I sense something different.
بطريقة ما أشعر بشيء مختلف.
(Five years ago?)
(منذ خمس سنوات مضت؟)
Weiwei.
ويوي.
(Five years ago) Please don't be mad, Weiwei.
(قبل خمس سنوات) من فضلك لا تغضب يا ويوي.
Let go of me.
(منذ خمس سنوات مضت)
(Five years ago) Don't be mad.
(قبل خمس سنوات) اتركيني.
I met her
التقيت بها
at a dinner with other investors.
على عشاء مع مستثمرين آخرين.
She was drunk
كانت في حالة سكر
and mistook me for someone else.
وأخطأني لشخص آخر.
Why did you go to the hotel with her
لماذا ذهبت إلى الفندق معها
when you knew she was drunk?
عندما علمت انها كانت في حالة سكر؟
It's a misunderstanding.
إنه سوء فهم.
Why do you act tough on me?
لماذا تتصرف بقسوة معي؟
Well, to be fair,
حسنًا ، لكي نكون منصفين ،
I can create a similar misunderstanding, can't I?
يمكنني خلق سوء فهم مشابه ، أليس كذلك؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
I never expected
لم أتوقع أبدا
Jiang Fengyan has been cheating on me
جيانغ فنغيان كان يخونني
after we got married.
بعد أن تزوجنا.
(I have some work to deal with in the office.)
(لدي بعض الأعمال لأتعامل معها في المكتب).
(I'll come back late.)
(سأعود متأخرًا.)
(Don't wait up.)
(لا تنتظر.)
Liar.
كذاب.
Fengyan.
فنغيان.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
Wei was aware of our relationship
كان وي على علم بعلاقتنا
but she chose to stay silent?
لكنها اختارت الصمت؟
It's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
Why?
لماذا؟
She isn't that smart.
هي ليست بهذا الذكاء.
When can I possess you as a whole?
متى يمكنني امتلاكك ككل؟
No rush.
لا داعي للاندفاع.
After the company goes public,
بعد طرح الشركة للاكتتاب العام ،
I'll belong to you.
سوف أنتمي لك.
(As long as we kill her,)
(طالما نقتلها)
(we can be together rightfully.)
(يمكننا أن نكون معًا بشكل صحيح.)
(Won't the police find this out?)
(ألن تكتشف الشرطة ذلك؟)
(I'll take care of everything well.)
(سأعتني بكل شيء جيدًا.)
(I can do anything)
(يمكنني أن أفعل أي شيء)
(for you.)
(لك.)
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Oh, gosh.
يا إلهي.
Wei.
وي.
You made no sound when you came in.
لم تصدر أي صوت عندما دخلت.
Why are you here
لماذا أنت هنا
at this late hour?
في هذه الساعة المتأخرة؟
I thought someone broke into
اعتقدت أن شخصا ما اقتحم
my house.
بيتي.
Do I have to inform you before I come to my brother's place?
هل يجب علي إبلاغك قبل أن أصل إلى منزل أخي؟
Isn't it necessary?
أليس من الضروري؟
Wei.
وي.
You act strangely today.
أنت تتصرف بغرابة اليوم.
You're different.
انت مختلف.
You haven't told me
أنت لم تخبرني
why do you come here at this late hour.
لماذا أتيت إلى هنا في هذه الساعة المتأخرة.
Well.
نحن سوف.
I'm going to prepare for my wedding tomorrow.
سأستعد لحفل زفافي غدًا.
So, my mom asked me to sleep at your place tonight.
لذا طلبت مني أمي أن أنام في مكانك الليلة.
By the way,
على فكرة،
she passed me this Chinese medicine.
أعطتني هذا الدواء الصيني.
It helps you to give birth to a son.
يساعدك على ولادة الابن.
(Mother-in-law)
(حماة " أم الزوج أو أم الزوجة)
Stand right there.
قف هناك.
Clean up the rubbish.
نظف القمامة.
Wei.
وي.
The cleaner is coming tomorrow.
المنظف قادم غدا.
Sleep with the rubbish then.
ثم نم مع القمامة.
I'll ask the cleaner
سأطلب المنظف
to sweep out you and the rubbish tomorrow morning.
لتنظيفك والقمامة صباح الغد.
I...
أنا...
What has gotten into her?
ما الذي حصل لها؟
Weiwei.
ويوي.
Have you reached home?
هل وصلت المنزل؟
The medicine works if you drink it at 10.30 p.m. sharp.
الدواء يعمل إذا شربته في تمام الساعة 10:30 مساءً.
This is your priority now.
هذه هي أولويتك الآن.
After all, Fengyan works finger to bone
بعد كل شيء ، فنغيان يعمل إصبعًا إلى عظم
(Mother-in-law) and he needs his own child to take over it.
(حماته) ويحتاج إلى طفله لتولي الأمر.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
everything he owns will go to outsiders.
كل ما يمتلكه سيذهب إلى الغرباء.
Oh, right.
صحيح.
Regarding the payment, I've talked to the property sales office.
بخصوص الدفع ، لقد تحدثت إلى مكتب مبيعات العقارات.
(I never expected my life winds up like this)
(لم أتوقع أن تنتهي حياتي بهذه الطريقة)
(after marrying Fengyan.)
(بعد الزواج من فنجيان.)
Fengyan.
فنغيان.
Yes?
نعم؟
I have something for you.
لدي شيء لك.
What's it?
ما هذا؟
Ta-da.
تا دا.
Your exclusive portrait.
صورتك الحصرية.
Whoa.
قف.
Did you draw this?
هل رسمت هذا؟
I drew this for you.
لقد رسمت هذا لك.
This is awesome.
هذا رائع.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
You're my precious girl.
أنت فتاتي الغالية.
Well.
نحن سوف.
Put it in your bedroom.
ضعه في غرفة نومك.
So it can remind you of me
لذلك يمكن أن يذكرك بي
when you look at the portrait
عندما تنظر إلى الصورة
before you sleep.
قبل أن تنام.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Mengmeng.
مينجمينج.
Yes.
نعم.
Well.
نحن سوف.
I'll get going.
سأذهب.
Take care.
يعتني.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
Okay.
تمام.
♪If you insist on leaving, I'll let you go♪
♪ إذا أصررت على المغادرة ، فسأطلق سراحك ♪
♪My love for you, I'll keep it♪
♪ حبي لك ، سأحتفظ به ♪
♪Encountering you in a different world♪
♪ مواجهتك في عالم مختلف ♪
♪I'm content♪
♪ أنا راضٍ ♪
♪With what I possessed before♪
بما كنت أملكه من قبل ♪
♪An unexpected love♪
♪ حب غير متوقع ♪
♪Is an abrupt blessing♪
هي نعمة فجائية
♪Regardless of whether your love is genuine or not♪
♪ بغض النظر عما إذا كان حبك حقيقي أم لا
♪Your place in my heart never changes♪
مكانتك في قلبي لا تتغير
♪Even if I have to be punished for falling for you♪
♪ حتى لو كان يجب أن أعاقب لوقوعك في حبك ♪
♪I'm not afraid of that♪
♪ لست خائفًا من ذلك ♪
♪Bring it on. I won't back down♪
اجلبه.  لن أتراجع ♪